techfunda.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Tech Funda

* * *

#### Privacy policy for TechFunda

Following statements describes our privacy policies:

  * We do not ask user to enter their personal information
  * All visits are logged for statistics and diagnosis purposes
  * We try our best to keep up the security settings to protect the sensitive information

####   
Personal User Information

TechFunda is free to visit and no registration is required. A visitor can navigate to any publically available pages of the website.

####   
Cookies

This website uses cookies, like other websites. Cookies are small text stored in your browser of the computer or mobile phone when you browse websites, that help us to provide you a better experience.

Cookies help us in following ways:

  * Continuously improve our website
  * Improve the speed of the site
  * Allows you to share pages wiith social sites
  * Offers services/content of your interest (by advertising)
  * Provided some data for advertisers or our team that help us keep the site free

Cookies are not used to

  * Collect any personally identifiable information (without your express permission)
  * Collect any sensitive information (without your express permission)
  * Pass personally identifiable data to third parties

You can use Browser settings to restrict the cookies however restricting cookies may disable some of the feature of the websites. Cookies are also used by Social websites like Facebook, Twitter for their features.  

####   
Visitor Statistics Cookies

We use Google Analytics to collect visitors statistics that in tern uses Cookies. Read more about [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/) (owned by Google) of the Google Analytics..

####   
Advertising Cookies

Cookies are widely used in online advertising. No one can gain personally identifiable information from these cookies.

You can learn more about online advertising, or opt-out of almost all advertising cookies at http://www.youronlinechoices.com. Opting out of advertising cookies doesn't disable ads but stops advertisers to tailor ads specific to you. Read more about DoubleClick - [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) owned by Google

#### Turning Cookies Off

Cookies can be disabled and switched off however this limits the functionality of most of the websites.

####   
Links

TechFunda may contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. This privacy document applies only to TechFunda.

For any questions about this privacy statement, please click on Contact link.
